迈克:好!再说一遍.滑雪旅行,
Mike: Alright!Say it one more time.
72个小时,23个女孩,30个男孩,
We got one ski trip, seventy two hours, twenty three women, thirty guys,
还有一个近视眼儿陪护.先生们,机会多多.
and one near sighted chaperone.Gentlemen, the possibilities rae endless.
埃迪:我就滑雪.
Eddie: Yeah, I'm only talking one ski.
鲍纳:我们家人肯定不会让我去的.
Boner: There's no way my folks are going to let me go.
迈克:鲍纳.你应该学会怎么对付那帮老家伙.
Mike: Boner.You just gotta learn how to handle old people.
鲍纳:迈克,你也没跟你父母说呢.
Boner: Mike, you haven't even talked to your parents yet.
迈克:好了,鲍纳.你真的认为我父母会对我说"不"么?
Mike: Come on Boner.Do you actually think that my parents could say no to me?
鲍纳:我知道,你也可以替我跟我爸妈说情的.
Boner: I know, you could talk to my mum and dad for me.
迈克:不,埃迪,去拿几把椅子.鲍纳,
Mike: No.Eddie, go get a couple of chairs, alright.Now Bone.Look.
听好了,我教你.我是你爸爸,埃迪你呢,鲍纳的妈妈.
I'll show you.I'll be your dad, and Eddie, you be Boners mum.
埃迪:好的,亲爱的.
Eddie: Yes dear.
迈克:好,开始.晚上,
Mike: Ok, it's evening at the Stabone residence and you and you charming
parents are sitting down for a lovely dinner
鲍纳:我爸爸通常会坐这儿.
Boner: My dad usually sits here.
迈克:好的.
Mike: Fine.
埃迪:把土豆递给我,呣,你爸爸叫什么名字,鲍纳?
Eddie: Pass the potatoes um, uh, what's your dad's name Boner?
鲍纳:西尔威斯特.
Boner: Sylvester.
迈克:等会儿.你爸爸叫西尔威斯特*斯泰本?
Mike: Wait a minute.Your dad's name is Sylvester Stabone?
鲍纳:谁知道?你管得着么?
Boner: Who knew?
迈克:好吧.
Mike: Yeah.Ok.So Richard, what is it you wanted to talk to us about?
鲍纳:开始说此次滑雪旅行.
Boner: Well, there is this ski trip.
迈克:滑雪旅行.我问你,
Mike: Ski trip.Ha.Now why would you want to go on a ski trip?
你为什么想参加滑雪旅行?你连怎么滑雪都不会.
You don't even know how to ski.
鲍纳:喂,伙计们.我可告诉你们了.他怎么都不会让我去的.
Boner: See guys.I told you.He aint going to even let me go.
迈克:鲍纳,只是演戏,来继续.
Mike: Boner, it's just for pretend.Come on.
鲍纳:哦!
Boner: Oh!
迈克:现在,为什么要我们允许你去,你有什么充分的理由?
Mike: Now give me one good reason why we should let you go.
鲍纳:女人.
Boner: Women.
迈克:女人?
Mike: Women?
埃迪:在我吃饭的的时候讨论这种事,我可不愿意.回你房间去,理查德.
Eddie: I will not have talk like this at my table.Go to your room Richard.
迈克:好了.听着,鲍纳.
Mike: Come on.Look Bone.You never say women in front of your parents.
以后,再也不要在父母面前谈女人,你要谈些崇高理想之类的东西,
You say stuff like class spirit.You say growth experience.
也可以谈谈成长的经历.什么都可以,就是不要谈女人.
But you never ever say women.
鲍纳:崇高理想.
Boner: Ok, class spirit.
迈克:对!
Mike: Right!
埃迪:成长经历.
Eddie: Growth experience.
迈克:对!
Mike: Yes!
所有人:女人!
All: Women!
开萝尔:你别把书本留在那儿.把书带回你房间去.别吃零食,会坏了你正餐的食欲.
Carol: Don't leave your book there.Take them to you room.No snacking.You'll spoil your dinner.
本:妈妈和爸爸生病了,开萝尔疯狂滥权.
Ben: Mum and dad are sick and carols mad with power.
开萝尔:还没收拾干净?
Carol: Is it clean yet?
本:我正在干吧,我正在干呢.
Ben: I'm working, I'm working.
迈克:嗨,等会儿.妈妈和爸爸生病了?哦,
Mike: Hey wait a minute.Mum and dad are sick?Oh this is perfect.
太棒了.我现在去请他们批滑雪旅行,趁他们还虚弱.
Now I can ask them about the ski trip while they are weak.
(上去到父母的房间)
(Goes up to parents room)
迈克:开萝尔刚才告诉我一个非常可怕的坏消息,
Mike: Carol just told me the awful news and well I just thought I'm come
我特地上来表达我的慰问之情.
in to offer my condolences.
麦琪:我们生病了,迈克,不过还没危及生命.
Maggie: We're sick Mike, not dead.
迈克:那么.那好好治.
Mike: Ok then.That settles it.
麦琪:治什么?
Maggie: Settles what?
迈克:是这么回事,本周末有次班级滑雪旅行,
Mike: Oh see, there was this class ski trip this weekend and I thought
我原本想放弃因为我想花些时间陪陪您俩.不过,很明显你俩也没得什么大病不需要那样.
I'd try to get out of it so I could spend some time palling around with
所以,我想去滑雪.
you guys.But obviously you are in no shape for that.So I got to go.
杰森:别想了,杰森.
Jason: Forget it Mike.
迈克:爸爸?
Mike: Dad?
杰森:英语你都还不及格,你哪儿也不许去.
Jason: You're not going anywhere while you are still flunking English.
迈克:时机非常好,爸爸.
Mike: Oh great timing dad.I mean, we had an English test today.
今天我们英语搞了个测试.我的意思是说,
I mean couldn't you have told me this before I took it.
在考试之前,您为什么不这么跟我说?
I mean if I'd known you would take this kind of an attitude,
如果我知道你会采取这种态度,我就会努力学习的.
I just may have studied for it.
杰森:啊,我感觉不好,比迈克的成绩还不好.
Jason: Ah, I feel worse than mike's grades.
麦琪:我也是.
Maggie: Me too.
杰森:我想再打个电话给医生.
Jason: I got to try again to call a doctor.
麦琪:你自己就是医生.
Maggie: You are a doctor.
杰森:哦,这可能就是为什么我打电话的时候总占线的原因吧.
Jason: Oh, I guess that's why I keep getting a busy signal.
埃迪:哦,希佛.等一下.哦,迈克迈克迈克.你肯定不会相信的.这绝对是破天荒的特大新闻.
Eddie: Oh Seaver.Wait up.Oh Mikey Mikey Mikey.You're not going to believe this.This has got to be the best news since Lucy came back to TV.
迈克:什么?
Mike: What?
埃迪:鲍纳!他父母允许他参加这次滑雪旅行.
Eddie: Boner!His folks are letting him go on the ski trip.
鲍纳:非常感谢,迈克.你不开心,不为我感到高兴么?
Boner: Thanks a lot Mikey.How come you aint sharing in my joy?
迈克:因为,我去不了了.
Mike: Cos I'm not going.
鲍纳和埃迪:什么?
Boner and Eddie: What?
迈克:对,我爸爸说我必须通过英语考试.
Mike: Yeah, my dad says I have to be passing English.
他在昨天考试完了才这么跟我说的.
He tells me this after yesterday's test.
埃迪:那,你肯定自己不及格?
Eddie: Well are you sure you flunked?
迈克:埃迪,好了.我们现在讨论的是我.醒醒闻闻你自己.
Mike: Eddie come on.This is me we're talking about.Wake up and smell yourself.
埃迪:迈克.只要有成绩曲线(注:成绩分布表,用以控制相对及格率),就会有希望.
Eddie: Well Mikey.As long as there's a grade curve, there's always a hope.
迈克:对,尤其是鲍纳在曲线内.
Mike: Hey, yeah you know, especially with Boner in the curve.
鲍纳:只要我能帮的一定帮.
Boner: I do what I can.
埃迪:你为什么不去找教员助理给帮帮忙呢?
Eddie: Why don't you go ask the teachers aid on this one.Hu?
迈克:太感谢了,伙计们.啊,嗨.
Mike: Hey, thanks a lot guys.Ah, hi.
罗宾:嗨,迈克.
Robin: Hi mike.
迈克:你叫鲍比?
Mike: Ah, Bobby right?
罗宾:罗宾.
Robin: Robin.
迈克:罗宾,对.
Mike: Robin, yeah.So Robin have you finished grading those tests from
罗宾,昨天的考卷你有没有改完?罗宾:你的成绩……
yesterday yet?Robin: Yeah.Your definition of a dangling participle was...
迈克:非常棒吧?
Mike: Inspired?
罗宾:糟透了.
Robin: Dirty.
迈克:噢,我该怎么办?
Mike: Well, how did I do overall?
罗宾:迈克,我没法儿告诉你.
Robin: Mike, I can't tell you.
迈克:哦,为什么?
Mike: Oh why?
罗宾:这是规定.
Robin: It's the rules.
迈克:好了,罗宾.我,
Mike: Come on Robin.I, I got to know.Whatever you want.
我一定得知道.你想要什么都行.我会把自己卖了换这消息.
I'll trade my body for the information.
罗宾:这算是邀请吗?
Robin: Is that an offer?
迈克:罗宾,我真的得知道这次成绩.
Mike: Ah, look Robin.I really need to know this grade.
如果我不及格,这次滑雪旅行就去不了了.
If I don't pass, I don't go on the ski trip.
罗宾:哦,你想去?
Robin: Oh, you're going?
迈克:对,如果我得C的话.好了,告诉我得了多少.
Mike: Yeah, if I get a C.So come on.Tell me what I got.
罗宾:你要得到C是吗.
Robin: What you got rhymes with C.
迈克:啊,学校马上会公布成绩么?
Mike: Ah, the school's giving out G's now?
罗宾:D+.
Robin: D plus.
迈克:D+. 有成绩曲线吗?
Mike: D plus.Is that with the curve?
罗宾:不可能.
Robin: It's with an incredible curve.
麦琪:你不会相信其余的人会是什么样子.
Maggie: You would not believe what the rest of the house looks like.
杰森:我会杀了这帮小崽子.我们就求他们给帮一个忙,
Jason: I'm going to kill those kids.
在我们生病的时候帮着打点家务.但是,
We asked them for one favor, will the help with the house while we're sick.
他们做了忙?没有.
But do they do it?No.
麦琪:杰森,家里很好.
Maggie: Jason, the house is perfect.
杰森:什么?
Jason: What?
麦琪:像医院,一尘不染,
Maggie: It's like a hospital out there.There is no dust.
衣服脏了有人给洗,吃晚饭的时候有人给摆桌子,
All the laundry's been done.The table is set for dinner.
本的衣服已经熨好了明天就可以穿.我从来没有见过这个家这么得井井有条过,
Bens little clothes have been ironed for tomorrow.
当然,是我生完孩子回去……上班之后
I haven't seen the house this organized since I went back to......work.
杰森:哦,好.非常好.你在告诉一个垂死的人说他有一个糟糕的家庭主妇.
Jason: Oh good.That's very good.You tell a dying man he's a bad house wife.
麦琪:哦,亲爱的.
Maggie: Oh, honey.Don't get upset.
别生气.开萝尔想做好只不过有点过头,
Carol just went a little over board trying to do a great job, and I just...
我只是……我是不是伤着你了,是么?
I've hurt your feelings haven't I?
杰森:不不不不,那不是什么大不了的.
Jason: No no no no, just it's really no big deal.
如果开萝尔做得比我强,那么我们应该为此感到高兴,
If Carol does a better job than I do,
因为她是一个好帮手.是不是?
then we should be grateful cos she's a big help.Right?
麦琪:是.
Maggie: Right.
杰森:但是,为了澄清起见,我们是在说她做的比我们好么?
Jason: And just to be clear, we are saying she does do a better job?
麦琪:哦,杰森.
Maggie: Oh Jason.
杰森:我们没有说,是你在说我在听.
Jason: No that's what we're saying, that's what I hear when you say...
麦琪:亲爱的.
Maggie: Honey.
杰森:那只是我听说的.
Jason: That's what I'm hearing.
麦琪:我真的不是那个意思.
Maggie: I really didn't mean that.
老师2:因为罗宾泄露了你昨天的考试成绩,
Teacher 2: As Robin passes out your tests from yesterday,
我必须告诉你我非常震惊,没有人的成绩在C以下.
I must say I was so shocked.No one got below a C.
我在寻求职业的帮助.
I'm seeking professional help.
迈克:A.我得了个A?罗宾,我得了个……A?
Mike: An A.I got an A?Robin I'm a.An A?
罗宾:我重新批了你的卷子.
Robin: I rechecked your paper.
迈克:可是查特尔老师会发现的,我是说她会明白是怎么回事.
Mike: Ah yeah, but Miss Charter's going to find out.I mean she'll know.
罗宾:她从来连卷子看都不看一眼,我办事你放心.
Robin: She never even sees the papers.You're safe with me.
你嘴唇那么张着,还挺有点可爱的.
You look kind of cute with your mouth hanging open like that.
迈克:耶!这下,我可以去滑雪了.
Mike: Yes!This means I can go on the ski trip.
听着,罗宾,我真的欠了你一个大人情.
Look Robin, I really owe you in a major way.
罗宾:用不着这么客气.
Robin: Well you're welcome in a major way.
迈克:如果有什么事我能帮你,我一定在所不辞.好么?
Mike: Look, if there is anything that I can do for you Robin, you got it.Ok?
罗宾:迈克.滑雪旅行.
Robin: Mike.The ski trip.
迈克:跟这有什么关系?
Mike: Yeah, what about it?
罗宾:我想在滑雪旅行中和你做伴.
Robin: I'd love to be your date on the ski trip.
迈克:什么滑雪旅行?
Mike: What ski trip?
罗宾:这次滑雪旅行.
Robin: The ski trip.
迈克:啊啊.不行,
Mike: Ah ha ha.No Robin, Robin.
罗宾,
See, none of us guys are taking dates on the ski trip because there are
罗宾.
going to be so many coyotes up there.
男生没有在滑雪旅行中找朋友的,因为那有很多小妞儿.
Yeah, those those hills are just crawling with coyotes (howls).
罗宾:迈克,你能去可多亏有我改了你的分数.
Robin: Mike, the only reason that you are able to go is that I changed your grade.
迈克:对,我非常感谢.
Mike: Yeah and I am very thank full for that.
罗宾:是么?
Robin: Are you?
迈克:哦!
Mike: Oh!
罗宾:有你脸上那副木鸡似的表情,你显得更可爱了.
Robin: You're even cuter with that dumb look on your face.
鲍纳:那就是说,有个女孩在逼你跟她共渡周末?
Boner: So a girl is forcing you to spend the weekend with her?
迈克:对.
Mike: Yes.
鲍纳:那这有什么不好么?
Boner: And this is a bad thing?
迈克:不好.
Mike: Yes.
埃迪:好,迈克.
Eddie: Ok Mikey, look at it this way.
这么看这件事.比方说你是个教员助理,你帮某个美女改分数.
Let's say you was a teachers aid and you were helping out a cute chick
那你想让别人怎么回报你?你明白了么?
with a phony grade.What would you expect in return?You see?
迈克:不不.完全不同的事情.
Mike: No no.Totally different situation.
埃迪:怎么不同?
Eddie: How?
迈克:如果我对待一个女孩就如她一直待我那样,那很明显,
Mike: Ok, if I treat a girl how she's been treating me,
那女孩会和我感觉到一样.是完全一致的.哦,
it would be obvious that, well, that the girl would feel as rotten as I do.
一样的.我成熟了.
It's no different.Oh no.I'm maturing.
埃迪和鲍纳:不!
Eddie and Boner: No!
埃迪:好,目前事实是这样的,
Eddie: Right, the facts here are;
如果这次滑雪旅行你不带罗宾一起去,
if you don't take Robin with you on the ski trip,
她就会把你的分数改回去,而你呢就别想去了.
she's going to change your grade back, and you can't go.
迈克:那我该怎么办?
Mike: Now what do I do?
鲍纳:我要是能有这苦恼该多好啊.
Boner: I wish I had problems like this.
埃迪:我这辈子是不会再跟女的约会了.他们了解我以后肯定不会喜欢我.
Eddie: You know I have never had a second date with a chick in my life.Girls never like me once they get to know me.
鲍纳:如果没有女孩了解我,
Boner: If no girls know me,
那我就会成为本校最得人缘的纨绔子弟.
I'd probably get to be the most popular dude in school.
迈克:嗨,开萝尔,我有事问你.
Mike: Hey carol, I need to ask you something.
开萝尔:脱鞋.
Carol: Take your shoes off.
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why?
开萝尔:地板我刚打的蜡.
Carol: I just waxed the floor.
迈克:好,开萝尔,我需要些建议,可以么?
Mike: Ok Carol look.I need some advice ok?
开萝尔:从妈妈那儿?
Carol: From mo?
迈克:干得好,好,开萝尔.咱们比方说,你真的是想得不行了,你打算搞定你喜欢的这个男生让他带你去玩.
Mike: Ok.Nice job.Ok now Carol.Let's say you were really desperate and you trapped this guy into going out with you.
开萝尔:咱们不这么比方.
Carol: Lets not.
迈克:好好.咱们比方说,
Mike: No no.Lets say you trapped him, because you liked him.
你喜欢他,你就套他.那他怎么做才能让你不喜欢他?
Now what could he do to make you not like him?
开萝尔:你认真的?
Carol: You're serious?
迈克:对.
Mike: Yeah.
开萝尔:好.首先,如果有男生会被套住,那他一定是个大弱智,我现在说的是极为弱智.
Carol: Ok.Well first, any guy who could be trapped into a date, is a
weak kneed winky.Now I am talking major winky
迈克:别说了,别说了.
Mike: Forget it.Forget it.
本:好,我打扫了我的房间,啊-----!(摔倒在地板上)
Ben: Ok, I cleaned my room and ahhhhhhhh!(Falls on the floor)
迈克:活干得真漂亮.
Mike: Very nice job.
杰森:请不要这么幸灾乐祸.
Jason: Place doesn't look so great.
迈克:嗨,爸爸.
Mike: Hey dad.
杰森:看!灰尘!她管这叫干净.呵.
Jason: Look!Dust!She calls this clean.Ah.
迈克:爸爸,我觉得这是您气头儿上的话.
Mike: Dad I think it's the fever talking.
杰森:哦,对,是我是我.
Jason: Oh yeah.It's me it's me.Everything else is just fine.
其它事都很好.等会儿,我知道,
Wait a minute; I know something that's not fine.
有些事不好.你英语成绩是怎么回事?啊?
What happened on your English test?Hu?
迈克:没什么,我得个A.
Mike: Alright, I got an A.
杰森:让我看看卷子.A!哇!
Jason: Let me see that test.A!Wow!
迈克:对,我根本就不用骗谁.
Mike: Yeah, I didn't even cheat on it.
杰森:"标点,冒号是你吃下食物,食物消化的地方."
Jason: "Punctuation, the colon is where food digests when you eat it."
迈克:这是在平均成绩之上的.
Mike: Ah, it was graded on a curve.
杰森:对,显然.
Jason: Yeah, apparently.
杰森:那就是说,
Jason: Well, I guess that means you're going to be able to go on that
无论如何你都可以去参加滑雪旅行了.
ski trip after all.
迈克:对,我觉得是吧.
Mike: Yeah, I guess so.
杰森:你对此不是特别的兴高采烈.
Jason: You don't sound too thrilled about it.
迈克:爸爸,我能问您些关于某些问题的建议么?
Mike: Dad, can I ask your advice about something?
杰森:为什么?
Jason: Why?
迈克:你是我爸爸,你喜欢给别人建议.
Mike: Well, you're my dad.You like that kind of stuff.
杰森:哦,对.
Jason: Oh yeah.
迈克:目前,如果有人帮了你忙,
Mike: Now, if somebody does you a favor, out of the blue,
是个大忙,但是你并没有要求他们这么做,
and it's a really great favor but you didn't ask them to,
而现在人家要你还人情,你会怎么办?
and now they want you to pay them back, what do you do?
杰森:在最初的时候,人就应该拒绝别人的好意.
Jason: Well, for starters you should refuse the favor.
杰森:你在开玩笑?
Mike: Are you kidding?
杰森:那,你还真的得还.
Jason: Well then you've got to pay them back.
迈克:这不是我想要的答案.
Mike: That was not the answer I was hoping for.
杰森:这和人这次滑雪旅行有关系么?
Jason: Does this have anything to do with the ski trip you're going on?
麦琪:你要去旅行?迈克,你过了?
Maggie: You're going?Mike you passed?
杰森:过了?他得了个A.
Jason: Passed?He got an A.
麦琪:A!哇!
Maggie: An A!Wow!Mike.Let me see that test.
迈克.让我看看卷子.昏迷是人头部被击打之后进入的深度睡眠状态.
Coma is a deep sleep you fall into after you get hit on the head."
杰森:这次在平均成绩之上.
Jason: It's graded on the curve.
麦琪:好,迈克,我觉得太棒了.
Maggie: Oh.Well Mike, I think it's wonderful.
杰森:耶耶耶,太棒了.
Jason: Yep yep yep.It's wonderful.Everything's wonderful.
一切都太棒了,最近咱们家一切都非常顺.
Everything's running very smoothly around here lately.
开萝尔:你们俩个还在做什么?好了.回楼上去.一会儿我就把你们的晚餐送上去.
Carol: Now what are you two doing up?Now come on.Back up stairs.I'll bring you dinner up in a little while.
杰森:我们晚餐有什么?
Jason: What are we having?
开萝尔:酒煨鸡.
Carol: Coq o vin.
杰森:我以前做过一次.
Jason: I made that once.
开萝尔:对,但是不用担心.我找到了本新菜谱.
Carol: Yeah, but don't worry.I found a new recipe.
杰森:我想去看看我的病人有没有打电话过来.托我的福,
Jason: Well I'm going to go see if any of my patients have called.
他们可能都治愈了.
With my luck, they're probably all cured.
麦琪:你爸爸还没醒过来呢,迈克得了个A.
Maggie: Your dad is still in shock.Mike got an A on a test.
开萝尔:A.我看看卷子.
Carol: An A.let me see that test.
麦琪:现在不行,开萝尔,
Maggie: Not now.Carol honey, listen.
亲爱的.你做得实在是太棒了,在我们生病的时候打理家务.
You are doing a terrific job at taking care of things while we are sick.
开萝尔:谢谢.
Carol: Well thanks.
麦琪:我有一个请求.
Maggie: I have just one request.
开萝尔:请讲.
Carol: Sure.
麦琪:别干了!
Maggie: Stop it!
开萝尔:什么?
Carol: What?
麦琪:你爸爸觉得你把家管得比他还好.
Maggie: You see your father is feeling like you are doing a better job of running the house that he does.
开萝尔:是.
Carol: I am.
麦琪:我知道.
Maggie: I know.
开萝尔:我只是想能替你们分忧解难.
Carol: All I wanted to do was help.
麦琪:那也是你爸爸想要的.但是,
Maggie: And that's what your dad wanted too.
把他想要的给他了,同时,你也使他不开心了.
But see, by giving him what he wanted, you've upset him.
开萝尔:把他想要的给他,同时,我让他不开心!
Carol: By giving him what he wanted I've upset him!
麦琪:对,亲爱的.你会明白的,
Maggie: Sure honey.You'll find out that most people hate it when they
大多数人都是这样,把他们想要的给了他们,他们反倒不开心了.
get what they want.
迈克:等等等会儿.这是真的么?
Mike: Wait wait wait a minute.Is this true?
麦琪:对.甚至还有一个中国人的咒语,
Maggie: Sure.There is even a Chinese curse which says,
它是这么说的,希望你得到你所想要的.
may you get what you wish for.
迈克:太对了.妈妈,
Mike: Ah this is perfect.
下一次如果我有麻烦,我会先找您.
Now mum, next time I have a problem, I'm coming to you first.
杰森:哦,我要回床睡觉了.
Jason: Oh, I'm going back to bed.
迈克:妈妈,我得去打个电话.
Mike: Mum, I've got to go make a phone call.
(滑倒在地板上)
(Slips on floor)
迈克:啊---------!
Mike: Ahhhhhhhhhhh!
麦琪:哦,你给地板打蜡了.
Maggie: Oh you waxed the floor.
迈克:你好,鲍纳么?哦,斯泰本先生.
Mike: Hello Boner?Oh Mr.Stabone.It's Mike.Yo to you too sir.
我是迈克.您也您也一样,先生.
Ah, is Richard there?Hello Boner.I need some help.
啊,是理查德么?嗨,鲍纳.
Well I'm going to ask Robin out tonight.
我需要帮助.我今晚打算请罗宾出来.现在,
Now I need you to tell me step by step exactly what you do on a
我需要你一步一步具体地告诉我你第一次约会是怎么做的,然后我就能把她给恶心走.不是说你的,没别的意思.
first date so I can completely gross this girl out.No offence.
罗宾:迈克,你在干什么?
Robin: Mike, what are you doing?
迈克:谁喜欢看电影的时候开点小差?
Mike: Who needs the distraction of a movie?
罗宾:不是我.
Robin: Not me.Ow!
迈克:哦,对不起.
Mike: Oh, I'm sorry.
罗宾:没关系.
Robin: That's ok.
迈克:罗宾,咱们俩谁也别跟谁闹了.
Mike: Look Robin, let's not kid each other.Alright?
好么?现在,你有需要,
Now you have needs and I have needs.
我也有需要.为什么在这么一个夜晚我们俩都非常的如饥似渴?
Now why should we both be needy on a night like this?
罗宾:迈克!
Robin: Mike!
迈克:美女,你马上就会成为一个真正的女人的.今晚,此时,此地.
Mike: Girl, you'll be a woman soon.Here, now, tonight.
罗宾:哦,迈克!好.
Robin: Oh Mike!Yes.
迈克:现在要不要来一大包什么零吃?
Mike: Ah, look wouldn't a nice big tub of something be good right now?
罗宾:爆米花?
Robin: Popcorn?
迈克:好主意.
Mike: Yeah, great idea.
鲍纳:他去哪儿了?
Boner: Where did he go?
埃迪:我不能告诉你.我的双筒望远镜都看不清了.
Eddie: I can't tell.My binocs are all fogged up.
鲍纳:迈克!
Boner: Mike!
迈克:伙计们,你们在这儿做什么呢?
Mike: Guys, what are you doing here?
埃迪:看电影.比我告诉你的看到的还要多.
Eddie: Catching a movie.Which is more than I can say for you.
迈克:伙计们,我不知道自己将要做什么.我把你们电话里告诉我的电影都试过了,确实起作用.
Mike: Guys.I don't know what I'm going to do.Now I've tried every sleazy
movie you gave me on the phone and they're working
鲍纳:别告诉我这个.那些话从来都不管用.
Boner: Don't give me that.Those lines never work.
埃迪:你试过没有,"美女,你马上就会成为一个真正的女人.今晚,此时,此地"?
Eddie: Have you tried "girl, you'll be a woman soon.Here, now, tonight."?
迈克:我试过了,她很投入.
Mike: Yeah, I tried it and she loved it.
埃迪:这话让我脸上跟挨了一拳似的.
Eddie: I got my face slapped for that.
迈克:这话让我脸上得到了一个吻.
Mike: I got my face kissed for it.
埃迪:等,你是怎么说的?
Eddie: Wait, how did you say it?
迈克:美女,你马上就会成为一个真正的女人.今晚,此时,此地.
Mike: Girl, you'll be a woman soon.Here, now, tonight.
鲍纳:哇!
Boner: Wow!
埃迪:我也是这么说的.
Eddie: That's how I say it.
鲍纳:埃迪,也许你应该想想自己是不是个碴子.
Boner: Well Eddie.Maybe you should consider the possibility that you're scum.
迈克:伙计们,伙计们!
Mike: Guys.Guys!Stop.Ok.Come on.
停,好吧.现在我需要一句肯定得让人冒火的话.
Now I need a line that is guaranteed to offend.
埃迪:鲍纳,把你最绝的话儿给他.
Eddie: Boner, give him your best line.
鲍纳:你看着她的眼睛,然后说,
Boner: You look her in the eye and you say, you got needs, I got needs,
你有需要,我也有需要,为什么在这么一个夜晚我们俩都非常的如饥似渴?
why should we both be needy on a night like this.
埃迪:这话我已经给她讲过了.
Eddie: I already gave him that line.
迈克:对,它确实有作用.
Mike: Yeah and it worked.
鲍纳:它从来没在我这儿起过作用.
Boner: It never worked for me.
迈克:你们这帮人一点忙都帮不了.
Mike: You guys are no help at all.
埃迪:我是碴子.
Eddie: I'm scum.
鲍纳:你是碴子.
Boner: You're scum.
罗宾:我以为你是去买爆米花了?
Robin: I thought you were going to get popcorn?
迈克:那不是精油制作的.
Mike: It wasn't real butter.
罗宾:那也让我讨厌.
Robin: Well I hate that too.
迈克:罗宾,我为什么今晚带你出来,你真的一点都不知道么?
Mike: Look Robin.Do you have any idea why I brought you here tonight?
罗宾:我有个绝妙的主意.
Robin: I've a pretty good idea.
迈克:不,你没有.
Mike: No you don't.
罗宾:不,我有.
Robin: Yes I do.
迈克:不,你没有.
Mike: No you don't.
罗宾:不,我有.
Robin: Yes I do.
迈克:听着,罗宾,
Mike: Look.Robin, I brought you here tonight so that I could totally gross
我今晚带你来这儿是因为我想,然后你就不再追我了.
you out so that you didn't like me anymore.
罗宾:你是为这个?
Robin: You did?
迈克:对.
Mike: Yeah.Well, what does a guy have to do around here to offend you, anyway?
罗宾:你就是那么做的.
Robin: You just did it.
迈克:好吧.最后我是这么做的.
Mike: Alright.Finally.
罗宾:我把自己的教员助理都快搭上了,就是为了你,而你就这么对我?
Robin: After I put my TA status on the line for you and this is how you treat me?
迈克:是在你把我的滑雪旅行搭上之后.
Mike: Well only after you put my ski trip on the line.
罗宾:我只是在跟你打趣.
Robin: I was just flirting.
迈克:罗宾,那就像是勒索,不像是打趣.打趣我还不明白.
Mike: Robin, that was blackmailing, not flirting.Flirting I know about.
罗宾:那你是肯定明白.比如,今天早上,你以身相许.
Robin: You sure do.Like this morning when you offered me your body.
迈克:罗宾,我跟哪个女孩都以身相许,
Mike: Robin, I offer every girl my body, alright.
好了吧.就是没人真的把我当回事.
Just nobody ever took me up on it.
罗宾:那我有什么错,
Robin: What's wrong with treating you the way that guys have been treating
用有史以来男人一直对待女人的方法对待你?
girls since the beginning of time?
迈克:有史以来.罗宾,我是从去年才开始约会的.
Mike: The beginning of time.Robin, I've only been dating for a year.
罗宾:好了,不要你担心.
Robin: Well don't worry.
你继续你的宝贝滑雪旅行好了,你不用和我呆在一起了.
You can go on your precious ski trip and you won't be stuck with me.
(哭)
(Crying)
迈克:好了,罗宾.
Mike: Come on Robin.Don't cry.What do you mean stuck?
不要哭了.呆在一起,你什么意思?
I just didn't want to be forced into doing something.
我只是不想被逼着去做什么事情.听好了,,
Look, just cause guys are crummy to girls doesn't mean that you have to
我觉得应该改变的男孩,而不是女孩.我知道,
be crummy to me.You know, I think it is the guys who ought to change.
这是个挺吓人的想法,是不是?
Not the girls.I know, pretty frightening concept isn't it?
埃迪:哇,看,她在哭.
Eddie: Wow, look at that.She's crying.
鲍纳:肯定是我教的话起作用了.
Boner: Must have been one of my lines.
迈克:啊,罗宾.我真想如果这一切从来从来没有发生该有多好.
Mike: Ah Robin.I just wish that none of this had ever ever happened.
罗宾:对.
Robin: You're right.
罗宾:我不应该勒索你.
Robin: I shouldn't have blackmailed you.
迈克:对.
Mike: Yeah.
罗宾:是我错了.
Robin: I was so wrong.
迈克:对.
Mike: Yeah.
罗宾:我根本不该重改你的分数.
Robin: I should have never changed your grade.
迈克:对,噢不.
Mike: Yeah.Uh no.
罗宾:明天我去把它纠正过来.
Robin: And tomorrow I'm going to make it right.
迈克:啊,明天.
Mike: Ah tomorrow.
罗宾:明天我去把你的分数改回到D+.
Robin: Tomorrow I'm going to change your grade back to a D plus.
迈克:我,你没必要……
Mike: I, you don't have to..
罗宾:谢谢你迈克.谢谢你帮我看清楚自己错在哪里.
Robin: And thank you Mike.Thanks for helping me see how wrong I was.
电视:新闻播报时间.现在是11点.您知道自己的孩子们现在身在何处么?
TV: Time for the news.It's eleven o clock.Do you know where your children are?
本:我还没有孩子.
Ben: I don't have any children.
开萝尔:啊.你睡觉时间过了两个小时,你眼睛还在睁着,你还把整个起居室扔的满地都是.
Carol: Ah.You're still up two hours after your bedtime and you've trashed the entire living room.
本:我会打扫干净的.
Ben: I'll clean it up.
开萝尔:不不,呆在那儿别动.怎么舒服怎么来.非常好.晚安本.
Carol: No, no, stay right where you are.Get comfortable.Perfect.Night Ben.
本:晚安爸爸.
Ben: Night dad.
杰森:晚安,开萝尔.本,你睡觉时间过了两个小时,你还没睡.
Jason: Night Carol.Ben, you're up two hours past your bed time.
本:好啊,她……
Ben: Well she ..
杰森:这儿乱七八糟都是怎么回事?
Jason: And what is this mess here?
本:我高兴.
Ben: I was set up.
杰森:本,把这些盘子拿出去到厨房,
Jason: Ben you take these dishes out to the kitchen and you get straight
现在马上上床.
up to bed right now.
本:我这就走,我这就走.
Ben: I'm going, I'm going.
杰森:看看这什么样了,花生奶油到处都是.
Jason: Look at this.Peanut butter all over the place.
迈克,你有没有份儿啊?
Mike are you responsible for any of this mess?
迈克:可能.
Mike: Probably.
杰森:你刚才去哪儿了?
Jason: Where have you been?
迈克:出去了,根据妈妈的建议.就你我,别告诉第三个人,这是我讫今为止得到的最次的建议.好了,爸爸,我英语考试的分数,明天之后就不再是A了,它将会是一个D+.
Mike: Out following mum's advice.And just between you and me dad, it was the worst advice I have ever got.Oh and dad.The grade on my English test, after tomorrow it won't be an A.I will be a D plus.
杰森:为什么?
Jason: Why?
迈克:我们老师
Mike: My teacher is throwing out the grade curve.
杰森:迈克,我感到非常的……
Jason: Well Mike, I am very...
迈克:失望,对我感到失望.我知道,我也失望.
Mike: Disappointed in me.Yeah, I know, me too.Well how do you think I feel?
你知道我的感觉么?滑雪旅行,还有所有那些个妙不可言的……班级精神,
I'm missing out on the ski trip and all that gorgeous...class spirit.
都没法领略了.爸爸,我只知道自从你们生病之后,
I mean dad, all I know is that nothing has been right since you've been sick.
就再没什么顺心的事.杰森:我突然感觉病好了许多.00:23:04,900
Jason: Suddenly I'm feeling much better.